# Yalikun Yilida

## Javascript/Front-End Developer

## **Summary**

A Frontend web developer has over 6 years of coding journy and with proven ability to collaborate effectively with team mates and senior developers while spending extra time to be mentored. Enjoy working closely with team members to ensure workloads are effectively redirected to bottlenecks and personally picking up the slack when necessary.

## **Experience**

#### **Five Gray Stone Tech (China)**

2016-2019

I co-founded and managed a web company with a group of colleagues, where our primary focus was to develop advertising platforms and websites to help local stores and small shops promote their products and locations. As a member of the development team, my role was to create the frontend of these platforms and websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and React. Additionally, I contributed to the development of backend applications using .NET and Node.js, and I also played a role in building backend services. Through my work at the company, I gained experience in both frontend and backend development, as well as collaborating with others to build effective solutions for our clients.

### **SWEDCON 18 AB** (Sweden)

Frontedn team lead 2022-08 2022-12

Worked as frontend team lead at SWEDCON 18 AB and contributed countless awesome solutions to their React / Next projects. Built body part picker system on patient application, hospital event managment calendar system and more.

## **Education**

#### **High School (China)**

September 2012 to June 2016

#### Lexicon Utbildning (Stockholm)

Jan 2022 to August 2012

#### **Science**

Graduated

#### IT Påbyggnad

**Fullstack Engineer** 

### **Skills**

Html/Html5

Css3, Sass, Bootstrap, Material-UI, Tailwind Css, Mantine css Javascript / Typescript

React / Next , Jest(Testing) Vue.js

Node.js / express, .Net core C#, SQL/NOSQL databses

## Contact





https://yalikun-dev.netlify.app/



eldar940818@gmail.com



Almbygatan 14, Spånga Stockholm 16376